Finding Aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Inventory of Getty Publications, 1954-2013 and undated IA10020
Institutional Records and Archives
- J. Paul Getty Museum, 1954-2000; 2003-2013,; undated; Series I.
  - Mark, Mary Ellen. Prom. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-23)
  - Martineau, Paul. Eliot Porter: In the Realm of Nature. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2013.IA.01-2)
  - Martineau, Paul. Herb Ritts: L.A. Style. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)
  - Morgan, Nigel J. Illuminating the End of Time:The Getty Apocalypse Manuscript. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2011.IA.01-09)
  - Paul, Carole, ed. The First Modern Museums of Art: The Birth of an Institution in 18th- and Early-19th-Century Europe. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)
  - Sciacca, Christine, ed. Florence and the Dawn of the Renaissance: Painting and Illumination: 1300-1350. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-23)
  - Woolett, Anne T., Yvonne Szafran, and Alan Phenix. Drama and Devotion: Heemskerck's "Ecce Homo" Altarpiece from Warsaw. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Baldwin, Gordon. Architecture in Photographs. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-3)
  - Berland, Dinah, au, ed. Some Japanese Flowers: Photographs by Kazumasa Ogawa. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
    Binding: String-tied.
  - Collins, Kristen, Peter Kidd, and Nancy K. Turner. The St. Albans Psalter: Painting and Prayer in Medieval England. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-3)
  - Danchev, Alex, ed, trans. The Letters of Paul Cézanne. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-3)
  - Freed, Leonard. This is the Day: The March on Washington. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
  - Heckert, Virginia. Ed Ruscha and "Some Los Angeles Apartments." Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
  - Hellert, Karen. The Window in Photographs. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-3)
  - Keene, Bryan C. Gardens of the Renaissance. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
  - Keller, Judith, and Amanda Maddox, eds. Japan's Modern Divide: The Photographs of Hiroshi Hayama and Kansuke Yamamoto. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
  - Lyons, Claire, Michael Bennett, Clemente Marconi, eds. Sicily: Art and Invention between Greece and Rome. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
  - Mayer, Lance, and Gay Myers. American Painters on Technique: 1860-1945. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
  - Nicholson, Elizabeth S. G., ed. Art & Science: A Curriculum for K-12 Teachers from the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
  - Raguin, Virginia Chieffo. Stained Glass: Radiant Art. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-3)
  - Schrader, Stephanie, ed. Looking East: Ruben's Encounter with Asia. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-1)
  - Weaver, Jeffrey and Madeline H. Caviness. The Ancestors of Christ Windows at Canterbury Cathedral. Los Angeles: 2013. (Box 2013.IA.01-3)
  - Belloli, Andrea. Gallery Earth: Discovering World Art. Los Angeles., undated (Box 2010.IA.01-03)
- Getty Conservation Institute (GCI), 1974-1998; 2000,; 2002,; 2006,; 2008-2013; Series II.
  The Getty Conservation Institute (GCI) works to advance conservation practice in the visual arts, broadly interpreted to include objects, collections, architecture, and sites. It serves the conservation community through scientific research, education and training, model field projects, and the broad dissemination of the results of both its own work and the work of others in the field. In all its endeavors, the GCI focuses on the creation and dissemination of knowledge that will benefit the professionals and organizations responsible for the conservation of the world's cultural heritage. The work of the Institute is carried out in four main areas: education, field projects, science, and communications.
  The Getty Conservation Institute is overseen by the J. Paul Getty Trust, a not-for-profit educational organization. The GCI is housed at the Getty Center in Los Angeles, along with the other programs of the Getty Trust. Its facility at the Center includes scientific laboratories, programmatic and administrative offices, and a conservation information center. In addition, the GCI maintains a laboratory at the Getty Villa, also in the Los Angeles area.
  Material comprises Getty publications by or about the Getty Conservation Institute and its activities.
  - Rinne, David. The Conservation of Ancient Marbles in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Malibu: 1974. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Corzo, Miguel Angel, ed.Wall Paintings of the Tomb of Nefertari, Scientific Studies for their Conservation: First Progress Report, July, 1987: A Joint Project of the Egyptian Antiquities Organization and the Getty Conservation Institute. Cairo and Century City: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Feilden, Bernard M. Between Two Earthquakes: Cultural Property in Seismic Zones. Marina Del Rey: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Feilden, Bernard M. Entre Dos Terremotos: Los Bienes Culturals en Zonas Sísmicas. Marina del Rey: 1987. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - Grimstad, Kirsten, ed. ICOM Committee for Conservation: 8th Triennial Meeting Sydney, Australia 6-11 September, 1987, Preprints Volume 1. Marina Del Rey: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Grimstad, Kirsten, ed. ICOM Committee for Conservation: 8th Triennial Meeting Sydney, Australia 6-11 September, 1987, Preprints Volume 2. Marina Del Rey: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Grimstad, Kirsten, ed. ICOM Committee for Conservation: 8th Triennial Meeting Sydney, Australia 6-11 September, 1987, Preprints Volume 3. Marina Del Rey: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Hodges, Henry W.M., ed. In Situ Archaeological Conservation: Proceedings of Meetings April 6-13 1986, Mexico. Century City: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Rockwell, Cynthia, comp.International Index on Training in Conservation of Cultural Property. Rome, Italy, and Marina Del Rey: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Ward, Philip. The Nature of Conservation: A Race Against Time. Marina Del Rey: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Ward, Philip. La Conservation du Patrimoine Culturel: Une Course Contre le Temps. Marina Del Rey: 1987., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Ward, Philip. La Conservación del Patrimonio: Carrera Contra Reloj. Marina Del Rey: 1987. (Box 1987.IA.04-12)
  - Brommelle, N.S. and Perry Smith, eds. Urushi: Proceedings of the Urushi Study Group, June 10-27, 1985, Tokyo. Marina del Rey: 1988. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Reedy, Terry J. and Chandra L. Reedy. Statistical Analysis in Art Conservation Research. Marina del Rey: 1988. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Selwitz, Charles. Cellulose Nitrate in Conservation. [Los Angeles]: 1988. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
    Series: Research in Conservation.
  - Cass, Glen R., James R. Druzik, Daniel Grosjean, William W. Nazaroff. Paul W. Whitmore, and Cynthia L. Wittman. Protection of Works of Art from Atmospheric Ozone. [Los Angeles]: 1989. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Grimstad, Kirsten, ed. The Conservation of Tapestries and Embroideries: Proceedings of Meetings at the Institut Royal du Patrimoine Artistique, Brussels, Belgium; September 21-24, 1987. [Los Angeles]: 1989. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Feller, R. L., M. Witt. Evaluation of Cellulose Ether for Conservation. Marina del Rey: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - ICOM Committee for Conservation. 9th Triennial Meeting: Dresden, German Democratic Republic, 26-31 August, 1990. Preprints, Volume II. Marina del Rey: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - International Conference on the Study and Conservation of Earthen Architecture. 6th International Conference on the Conservation of Earthen Architecture; Adobe 90 preprints: Las Cruces, New Mexico, U.S.A., October 14-19, 1990. Los Angeles: 1990. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - International Seminar on the Conservation of Cultural Property within the Urban Environment: Quito, Ecuador, November 1990: Introduction and Provisional List of Participants. Peru: 1990. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - International Seminar on the Conservation of Cultural Property within the Urban Environment: Quito, Ecuador, November 1990: Programme. Peru: 1990. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - International Seminar on the Conservation of Cultural Property within the Urban Environment: Quito, Ecuador, November 1990: English summaries of working documents. Peru: 1990. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - A Proposal for the Conservation of the Great Sphinx, Presented to the Egyptian Antiquities Organization by the Getty Conservation Institution, February 1990. Los Angeles: 1990. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Cather, Sharon, ed. The Conservation of Wall Paintings: Proceedings of a Symposium Organized by the Courtauld Institute of Art and the Getty Conservation Institute; London; July 13-16, 1987. Marina del Rey: 1991. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Scott, David A. Metallography and Microstructure of Ancient and Historic Metals. Marina del Rey: 1991. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - The Conservation of the Orpheus Mosaic at Paphos, Cyprus. Marina del Rey: 1991. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Grimes, Teresa. Los Angeles Landmarks: Reflections of Our Past and Symbols for Our Future. 1992. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - In the Tomb of Nefertari: Conservation of the Wall Paintings. Santa Monica: 1992. (Box 1987.IA.04-13)
  - Karp, Cary, ed. The Conservation and Technology of Musical Instruments: A Bibliographical Supplement to Art and Archaeology Technical Abstracts, Volume 28. Marina del Rey: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Reedy, Terry J, and Chandra L. Reedy. Principles of Experimental Design for Art Conservation Research. Marina del Rey: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - Selwitz, Charles. Epoxy Resins in Stone Conservation. Marina del Rey: 1992. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - The China Project: The Grottoes at Mogao and Yungang. 1993. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Corzo, Miguel Angel, and Mahasti Afshar, eds. Art and Eternity: the Nefertari Wall Paintings Conservation Project, 1986-1992. Santa Monica: 1993. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Grimes, Teresa. Heritage Education in Los Angeles County. 1993. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Conservation of Ancient Sites on the Silk Road: October 3-8, 1993, Mogao Grottoes at Dunhuang: Abstract & Programs/International Conference on the Conservation of Grotto Sites. Marina del Rey: 1993. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Hodges, Henry W. M., ed. Conservation Arqueologica in Situ; Memoria de las Reuniones, 6-13 Abril, 1986, Mexico. Santa Monica: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Mac Lean, Margaret G. H. Cultural Heritage in Asia and the Pacific: Conservation and Policy: Proceedings of a symposium held in Honolulu, Hawaii, September 8-13, 1991. Marina del Rey: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Nazaroff, William W., Mary P. Ligocki, Lynn G. Salmon, Glen R. Cass, Theresa Fall, Michael C. Jones, Harvey I. H. Liu, and Timothy Ma. Airborne Particles in Museums. Marina del Rey: 1993. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Scientific Program Research Conference II, Sponsored by the Getty Conservation Institute, May 18-19, 1993. 1993. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Van der Reyden, D., A. R. deTorres, L. Van Zelst, and D. Kresh. Seminar on Preventive Conservation in Latin America, August 19-20, 1993, Washington, D.C. Washington D.C.: 1993. (Box 2011.IA.01-07)
  - Afshar, Mahasti, Miguel Angel Corzo, Anna Maria Donadoni Roveri, Paolo Mora, Laura Mora. Nefertari, Luce d'Egitto: Catalogo a Cura di Miguel Angel Corzo; Mostra Ideata da Mahasti Afshar; a Cura di Julian Zugazagoitia. Rome: 1994. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
    Catalog of an exhibition held at the Palazzo Ruspoli in Rome, Oct. 6, 1994-Feb. 19, 1995. At head of title: Fondazione Memmo [and] The Getty Conservation Institute.
  - Druzik, James R., ed. Research Abstracts of the Scientific Program: GCI Scientific Program Report, December 1994. Marina del Rey: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-37)
  - Feller, Robert L. Accelerated Aging: Photochemical and Thermal Aspects. Marina del Rey: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Greenfield, Lauren, ed.Picture LA: Landmarks of a New Generation. Marina del Rey: 1994., (2 copies) (Box 1987.IA.04-13)
  - Rockwell, Cynthia, comp. 1994 International Directory of: Training in Conservation of Cultural Heritage. Marina del Rey: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Scott, David A., Jerry Podany, Brian B. Considine, eds. Ancient & Historic Metals: Conservation and Scientific Research: Proceedings of a symposium organized by the J. Paul Getty Museum and the Getty Conservation Institute; November, 1991. Marina del Rey: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Scott, David A., Pieter Meyers, eds. Archaeometry of Pre-Columbian Sites and Artifacts: Proceedings of a Symposium organized by the UCLA Institute of Archaeology and the Getty Conservation Institute, Los Angeles, California; March 23-27, 1992. Marina del Rey: 1994. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Wallert, Arie, Erma Hermens, and Marja Peck, eds. Historical Painting Techniques, Materials, and Studio Practice: Preprints of a Symposium, University of Leiden, the Netherlands, 28-29 June 1995. Marina del Rey: 1995. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
    Condition: Front cover has a 2" vertical slash in the center. Does not go through additional pages.
  - Gibson, Glenda Anne, ed. Picture Cape Town: Landmarks of a New Generation. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - MacDonald, John K. House of Eternity: the Tomb of Nefertari. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - MacDonald, John K. House of Eternity: the Tomb of Nefertari (Japanese version). Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Price, Nicholas Stanley, M. Kirby Talley Jr., and Alessandra Melucco Vaccaro, eds. Historical and Philosophical Issues in the Conservation of Cultural Heritage. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - Striegel, Mary F., and Jo Hill. Scientific Tools for Conservation: Thin-Layer Chromatography for Binding Media Analysis. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 1987.IA.04-13)
  - Striegel, Mary F., and Jo Hill. Scientific Tools for Conservation: Thin-Layer Chromatography for Binding Media Analysis. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
  - Tolles, E. Leroy, Edna E. Kimbro, Frederick A. Webster, and William S. Ginell. Survey of Damage to Historic Adobe Buildings after the January 1994 Northridge Earthquake. Los Angeles: 1996. (Box 1987.IA.04-13)
  - Ball, Tevvy, ed. La Conservation des Sites Archéologiques dans la Région Méditerranéenne: Une Conférence International Organisée par le Getty Conservation Institute et le J. Paul Getty Museum, mai 1995. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - ¡Camara! Ciudad de Mexico: Monumentos de Una Nueva Generación = Picture Mexico City: Landmarks of a New Generation. [Los Angeles]: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Conservación de vidrieras históricas análysis y diagnóstico de su deterio: restauración / [seminario organizado por el Getty Conservation Institute y la Universidad Internacional Menéndez y Pelayo, en conjuncto del Instituto de Conservación y Restauración de Bienes Culturales] Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 1987.IA.04-13)
  - De la Torre, Marta, ed. The Conservation of Archaeological Sites in the Mediterranean Region: An international Conference Organized by the Getty Conservation Institute and the J. Paul Getty Museum, 6-12 May, 1995. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Goldstone, Bud, Arloa Paquin Goldstone. The Los Angeles Watts Towers. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Klein, Kathryn, ed. The Unbroken Thread: Conserving the Textile Traditions of Oaxaca. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-22)
  - Klein, Kathryn, ed. El Hilo Continuo: La Conservación de las Tradiciones Textiles de Oaxaca. Los Angeles: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-22)
  - Picture Mumbai: Landmarks of a New Generation. [Los Angeles]: 1997. (Box 2012.IA.01-06)
  - Afshar, Mahasti, ed. Picture Paris: Monuments d'une novelle génération / Landmarks of a new Generation. [Los Angeles]: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Dardes, Kathleen and Andrea Rothe, eds. The Structural Conservation of Panel Paintings: Proceedings of a Symposium at the J. Paul Getty Museum, April 24-28, 1995. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Dorge, Valerie, and F. Carey Howlett, eds. Painted Wood: History and Conservation: Proceedings of a Symposium Organized by the Wooden Artifacts Group of the American Institute for Conservation of Historic and Artistic Works and the Foundation of the AIC, held at the Colonial Williamsburg Foundation; Williamsburg, Virginia, 11-14 November, 1994. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
  - MacLean, M. & B. H. Davis. Time & Bits: Managing Digital Continuity. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 1987.IA.04-13)
  - Maekawa, Shin, ed. Oxygen-Free Museum Cases. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 1987.IA.04-13)
  - Selwitz, Charles, and Shin Maekawa. Inert Gases in the Control of Museum Insect Pests. Los Angeles: 1998. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Corzo, Miguel Angel, ed. Mortality Immortality? The Legacy of 20th-Century Art. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-35)
    Archivally boxed by Conservation Dept. Over-cover is underneath book itself.
  - Derrick, Michele R., Dusan Stulik, James M. Landry. Infrared Spectroscopy in Conservation Science: Scientific Tools for Conservation. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Dorge, Valerie, Sharon L. Jones, comps. Building an Emergency Plan: A Guide for Museums and Other Cultural Institutions. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Dorge, Valerie, Sharon L. Jones, comps. Creación de un Plan de Emergencia: Guía para Museos y Otras Instituciones Culturales. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
    Condition: Archives copy has severe crumpling in lower back. Copy is still readable.
  - Dorge, Valerie, Sharon L. Jones, comps. Établir un plan d'urgence: Guide pour les musées et autres établissements culturels. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Economics and Heritage Conservation: A Meeting Organized by the Getty Conservation Institute, December 1998, Getty Center, Los Angeles. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2010.IA.01-02)
  - Kumar, Rakesh, and Anuradha V. Kumar. Biodeterioration of Stone in Tropical Environments: An Overview. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Piqué, Francesca, and Leslie H. Rainer. Les Bas-reliefs d'Abomey: L'Histoire Racontée Sur les Murs. African version of "Palace Sculptures of Abomey: History Told on Walls." Mali: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
    Published by Editions Jamala; Bamako, Mali.
  - Piqué, Francesca, and Leslie H. Rainer. Palace Sculptures of Abomey: History Told on Walls. Los Angeles: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
    Condition: Lower right corner of book slightly dented, as if dropped slightly.
    Co-published by J. Paul Getty Museum.
  - Pique, Francesca, and Leslie H. Rainer. Wall Sculptures of Abomey. United Kingdom version of "Palace Sculptures of Abomey: History Told on Walls." London: 1999. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
    Published by Thames & Hudson, London.
  - Avrami, Erica, Randall Mason, and Marta de la Torre. Values and Heritage Conservation: Research Report. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Avrami, Erica, Randall Mason, and Marta de la Torre. Values and Heritage Conservation: Research Report. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2008.IA.01-02)
  - Barkan, Elazar and Cynthia Scott. Local Heritage Preservation Project: Theory, Practice and Process: A Case Study Report and Survey of Literature and Practice. 2000. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Teutonico, Jeanne Marie, and Gaetano Palumbo, eds. Management Planning for Archaeological Sites: An International Workshop Organized by the Getty Conservation Institute and Loyola Marymount University; 19-22 May, 2000; Corinth, Greece. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Tolles, E. Leroy, Edna E. Kimbro, Frederick A. Webster, and William S. Ginell. Seismic Stabilization of Historic Adobe Structures: Final Report of the Getty Seismic Adobe Project. Los Angeles: 2000. (Box 2010.IA.01-01)
  - Whitfield, Roderick, Susan Whitfield, and Neville Agnew. Cave Temples of Dunhuang: Art and History on the Silk Road. London: 2000. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
    Published by British Library, but copyright 2000 by J. Paul Getty Trust.
  - Johnston-Feller, Ruith. Color Science in the Examination of Museum Objects: Nondestructive Procedures: Tools for Conservation. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Schaeffer, Terry T. Effects of Light on Materials in Collections: Data on Photoflash and Related Sources. Los Angeles: 2001. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - Clottes, Jean. World Rock Art. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Florian, Mary-Lou, Dale Paul Kronkright, Ruth E. Norton. The Conservation of Artifacts Made from Plant Materials. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Scott, David A. Copper and Bronze in Art: Corrosion, Colorants, Conservation. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-11)
  - Taller: Metodologia y Aplicaciones para Intervenciones en Retablos de Madera Policromada: Sevilla del 12 al 16 de Mayo de 2002. Los Angeles: [2002]., (2 copies). (Box 2013.IA.01-2)
  - Tolles, E. Leroy, Edna E. Kimbro, and William S. Ginell. Planning and Engineering Guidelines for the Seismic Retrofitting of Historic Adobe Structures. Los Angeles: 2002. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
    Series: GCI Scientific Program Reports.
  - Lavédrine, Bertrand. A Guide to the Preventive Conservation of Photograph Collections. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Leonard, Mark, ed. Personal Viewpoints: Thoughts about Paintings Conservation: A Seminar Organized by the J. Paul Getty Museum, the Getty Conservation Institute, and the Getty Research Institute at the Getty Center, Los Angeles; June 21-22, 2001. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
  - Maekawa, Shin, and Kerstin Elert. The Use of Oxygen-Free Environments in the Control of Museum Insect Pests. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-07)
    Series: Tools for Conservation.
  - Teutonico, Jeanne Marie, and Frank Matero, eds. Managing Change: Sustainable Approaches to the Conservation of the Built Environment: 4th Annual US/ICOMOS International Symposium Organized by US/ICOMOS, the Graduate Program in Historic Preservation of the University of Pennsylvania, and the Getty Conservation Institute; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania; April 2001. Los Angeles: 2003. (Box 2012.IA.01-08)
  - Bomford, David, and Mark Leonard, eds. Issues in the Conservation of Paintings. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-18)
    Series: Readings in Conservation.
  - Bomford, David, and Mark Leonard, eds. Issues in the Conservation of Paintings. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - Gavrilović, Predag, William S. Ginell, Veronika Sendova, Lazar Šumanov. Conservation and Seismic Strengthening of Byzantine Churches in Macedonia. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-08)
  - Learner, Thomas J. S. Analysis of Modern Paints. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-08)
  - Piqué, Francesca, Dusan C. Stulik, eds. Conservation of the Last Judgement Mosaic: St. Vitus Cathedral, Prague. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-08)
  - Stulik, Dusan, David Miller, Herant Khanjian, Narayan Khandekar, Richard Wolbers, Janice Carlson, and W. Christian Petersen. Solvent Gels for the Cleaning of Works of Art. Edited by Valerie Dorge. Los Angeles: 2004. (Box 2012.IA.01-30)
  - De La Torre, Marta, Margaret G. H. MacLean, Randall Mason, David Myers. Heritage Values in Site Management: Four Case Studies. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-12)
    Included: CD: "Supporting Documents for Heritage Values in Site Management: Four Case Studies."
  - Wheeler, George. Alkoxysilanes and the Consolidation of Stone. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-08)
  - Agnew, Neville and Janet Bridgeland, eds.Of the Past, for the Future: Integrating Archaeology and Conservation. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Ben Abed, Aїcha, ed. Stories in Stone: Conserving Mosaics of Roman Africa. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Ben Abed, Aїcha. Tunisian Mosaics: Treasures from Roman Africa. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Grzywacz, Cecily M. Monitoring for Gaseous Pollutants in Museum Environments. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)